ticketbar.eu 2018-09-05

# Privacy Policy

In this privacy policy we provide an explanation of the way in which we collect and use personal data. This Privacy Policy applies to all personal data that we process in regard to you when you contact us.

## Who we are:

We are Ticketbar.eu, part of Rokin Group Internacional SL based at Avenida de Carlemany 121-3, Escaldes-Engordany, AD700 Andorra

Ticketbar.eu processes and analyzes data with the aim of responding as well as possible to your needs as a customer. Ticketbar.eu is responsible for collecting and using your personal information as described in this privacy policy. Ticketbar.eu attaches great value to its role and reputation as a reliable business partner and thus also the guarantee to the right to privacy for you as a customer (or supplier). For questions, comments or complaints regarding the processing of your data, please contact us at [customerservice@ticketbar.eu](mailto:customerservice@ticketbar.eu).

## The type of personal information that we process:

Personal data are all data that can be directly or indirectly related to you. We may collect and process the following categories of personal information:

## Name and other identifiable information

For example, we can record your name, title, gender and date of birth.

## Your contact details and details about your personal account or registration

Your contact details may include your address, location, telephone number and e-mail address. If you register for a specific service or create a personal account, we can also record your login details and other information that you enter in the account or registration form.

## Our communication with you

If you send us an e-mail or message via social media, we will record your communication with us. When you call us, we record your questions or complaints in our database.

## Information that we collect when you use our website

When you visit our website, we can record your IP address, browser type, operating system, referring website, surfing behaviour and click behaviour. With your permission we can also receive your location data.

In addition, we can receive an automatic notification if you open a newsletter or click on a link in a newsletter.

## Information that you share with us

You can choose to share information with us, for example if you respond to social media or fill in a customer survey.

## Cookies and similar technologies

If you use our website, we collect information via cookies and similar technologies. For more information, read our cookie policy on the website.

## How we collect your data?

Ticketbar.eu can obtain your personal data in a number of ways, for example when you fill in a form, communicate with us via social media or register for our newsletter. Depending on your social networking settings, we may also receive information from the provider of your social network.

## The purposes for which we use your data:

The main purposes for which we use your personal information are:

## To provide services to you

To simplify the use of our online services for you, we may analyze the data collected by you from your use of our digital media and combine them with information collected through cookies and similar technologies. For example, to know which digital channel (e-mail, social media) or device (desktop, tablet or mobile) you prefer so that we can focus our communication on that channel or device.

## To communicate with you

We use your contact information to communicate with you, answer your questions or handle your complaints.

## For statistical research

We use automatic tools to carry out statistical research regarding general trends of the use of our services, website and social media and the behaviour of the preferences of our customers and users. Through statistical research we can develop better services. In addition, we can improve the design and content of our website.

In carrying out our research we can combine and analyze the different types of data. We only use aggregated data and do not use names, e-mail addresses or other directly identifiable information. We will not use sensitive data for this statistical investigation without your consent.

## For direct marketing purposes

We may use your personal information to send you newsletters or other marketing messages. To know what is relevant to you, we can use automatic tools to analyze your personal information. For this purpose, we can use and combine the information described above. We can also combine such aggregated information with information that we receive from public sources. We will not use your sensitive data for statistical research without your consent.

We use the results of our analysis to tailor our marketing messages to your specific interests and preferences. For example, if our analysis shows that you may be interested in certain types of services, we can modify our newsletter and website with content that we think are relevant to you.

We can use different channels for our marketing messages, such as e-mail and social media. You can revoke your permission to send marketing messages or make an objection at any time. For this, follow the instructions in the relevant marketing message or contact us at [customerservice@ticketbar.eu](mailto:customerservice@ticketbar.eu).

## Disclosure and sharing of data with third parties

We may disclose or share your personal information with third parties for the following purposes:

## For the support services that we offer

We use third parties, such as social network providers and marketing agencies, to provide our services. All these third parties are required to adequately protect your personal information and to process it only in accordance with our instructions.

## For statistical research and direct marketing

We may use your personal information for the purposes of statistical research and direct marketing (see above).

## Third party websites

Our website contains links to third party websites. If you follow these links, you will leave our website. This privacy policy does not apply to third party websites. Ticketbar.eu accepts no liability for the use of your personal data by these third parties. Your use of these websites is at your own risk. See the privacy policy of these third parties (if available) on how they handle your personal information.

## Within Ticketbar.eu

Your data can be shared with other colleagues within Ticketbar.eu, in order to provide you with the best possible service.

## Security and preservation

Ticketbar.eu takes the necessary technical and organizational measures to protect your personal data against loss or unlawful use. Your personal data will be kept for as long as necessary for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy or to the extent necessary to comply with laws and regulations and to resolve disputes.

## Child privacy

Ticketbar.eu strives not to collect information about children aged 16 or younger, or to create interest segments that are specifically designed to target children. If you are concerned about the privacy of your child in connection to our services, or if you believe that your child has entered personally identifiable information on our website, you can contact us at [customerservice@ticketbar.eu](mailto:customerservice@ticketbar.eu).

## Your rights

You have a number of rights when we record personal data about you. These rights are laid down in the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR). You can view, correct, block or delete your personal details at any time. You can contact us via [customerservice@ticketbar.eu](mailto:customerservice@ticketbar.eu) if you have questions, comments or complaints about this privacy policy.

Ticketbar.eu, part of Rokin Group Internacional  
SL Avenida de Carlemany 121-3 Escaldes-Engordany,  
 AD700  
Andorra

## How is this privacy policy kept

This privacy policy is effective per 1 May, 2018 and replaces our previous privacy policy. This privacy policy is constantly subject to review. We inform you about changes by publishing the revised policy on Ticketbar.eu, after which it will take effect immediately.
